



OBJECTIVE

3.5 years of IT industry experience encompassing a wide range of skill sets as PHP, Java Script, HTML, CSS, with PL/SQL implementation and support with technical skills. To attain a position in an organization to contribute my knowledge, skills and imaginative thinking to the best of my capabilities for the advancement of the company while studying and making myself grow with thecompany.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

Degree	Institution	Year of Passing	Board/University	
MCA	Dehradun Institute of Technology,uttarakhand	2016	Dit	6.08/10 CGPA
BCA	Modern Institute of Technology,uttarakhand	2013	Hemvati Nandan Bahuguna Garhwal University	66.38%
12 th	G.I.C Bhrigukhal, uttarakhand	2010	CBSC	64.31%
10 th	G.I.C Bhrigukhal, uttarakhand	2007	CBSC	53.67%

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• Operating Systems: Windows (XP, 2007, 2010), Linux (Ubuntu).

Languages: PHP,HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery Bootstrap,AWS

• IDE & Tools: Android Studio, Visual Studio Code.

Framework Codeigniter, laravel

Cms WordPressDatabases: SQL, MySQL.

Others: M.S Word, Excel, Power point.

REAL TIME PROJECTS

PROJECT TITLE: gurumannutrition (completed)

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MySQL database (WordPress) **Description:** It's a ecommerce project where client sell his supplement. **Platform Used:** PHP Programming and MySQL database (WordPress)

Team Size: Individual

Description: It's an training course project where user purchase course then after login redirect to user in Moodle

site where user attend online classes.

PROJECT TITLE: CRM

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MySQL database (Framework Codeignitor)

Description: basically this crm use for get leads in Facebook or Instagram then store the leads in goggle drive after that fetch leads and distribute to individual B.d.

URL: https://designoweb.work/crm

PROJECT TITLE: Foodivry

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MySQL database (Framework Laravel).

Description: It's a food ordering app and web in which a user can buy a food according to his/her requirement.

URL: http://foodivry.com/

PROJECT TITLE: hammerandspanner

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MySQL database (Framework Codelgniter)

Description: It's an app and web in which a user can request for plumber service according to his/her requirement.

URL: https://www.hammerandspanner.in/

PROJECT TITLE: dwear

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MySQL database (Framework Codelgniter)

Team Size: 2

Description: It's an app and web in which a user can request for product .it's a ecommerce site with multivendor .

URL: http://dwear.in/

PROJECT TITLE: twerkcycle

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MySQL database (Framework Code igniter)

Team Size: Individual

Description: It's a Twerk Cycle app in which the user will register himself and enter his details and according to his

workout plan, the related video and excise will be preferred.

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MySQL database (Framework Code igniter)

Team Size: Individual

PROJECT TITLE: Nozol

Description: It's a Hotel Booking App user can book room then admin approve and assign a room number to user according his/her requirement. User can chat to direct admin through firebase chat .

URL: https://nozol-hospitality.com/

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MySQL database (Framework CodeIgniter)

Team Size: Individual

Description: It's a Hotel Booking App user can book room then admin approve and assign a room number to user

according his/her requirement and chat to admin.

URL: https://nozol-hospitality.com/

PROJECT TITLE: Healthcliqs

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MYSQL Database (Framework Codelgniter)

Description: It's a ecommerce project where user can by medicine.

URL: https://healthcligs.com/b2b/

PROJECT TITLE: rajput tutorials

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MYSQL Database (Framework CodeIgniter)

Description: It's a elearning project where student purchased courses and attend online classes and convert to online classes to video and show them different bitrate(px). work also in mobile application api . use aws service like live classes and harvest job.

URL: https://rtpscschool.com/

PROJECT TITLE: Etgan Academy

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MYSQL Database (Framework CodeIgniter)

Description: It's a elearning project where student purchased courses and attend online classes and convert to online classes to video and show them different bitrate(px). work also in mobile application api . use aws service like live classes and harvest job.

PROJECT TITLE: Made easy

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MYSQL Database (Framework CodeIgniter)

Description: It's a elearning project where student purchased courses and attend online classes and convert to online classes to video and show them different bitrate(px). work also in mobile application api . use aws service like live classes and harvest job.

Platform Used: PHP Programming and MYSQL Database (Framework Codeigniter)

Description: It's a elearnig purpose project where user access courses in and attemp classes .

Experience

AppSquadz Software Private Limited

Jan 2021 - Till Date

- Created e-commerce platform with Codeignitor framework for launch of Ecommerce website.
- working on E learnig project like made easy,rajput tutorial etqan academy etc. to create live classes throught
 aws imlement in web and mobile app where user whom buy courses can attend live classes with chat
 functionality also work on aws harvest job where convert live classes to video where user also download and
 watch those online classes video.

Designo Web Technology

October 2019 - Oct 2020

- Provided creative input for making the website dynamic interactive and user-friendly.
- Troubleshoot problems in code and maintain existing websites
- Practice best and standard coding practices in all projects
- Developed , enhanced and maintained multiple websites by designing, coding and implementing SQL & access database.

Wrote server-side and client-side code for projects using PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript, specifically with Codeignitor framework.

Cuminte Pvt. Ltd Oct 2017 - Sep 2019

Work on wordpress website customize plugin and theme according to client requirements.

Work on moodle and core php implement new functionality to website .

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name : varun negi

Father's Name : Mr. Sumanchand singh negi

Mother's Name : Mrs. Maya Devi Date of Birth : 1 5 /10/1991

Gender : Male

Languages Known : English, Hindi, Garhwali

Marital Status : Single Nationality : Indian

Hobbies : Playing Cricket, Bollyball

COMPETENCIES

- Confident and Reliable
- Good team working skills
- Quick Learner
- Adaptable

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the above mentioned details are genuine and correct to best of my knowledge

Date:

Place: Noida (Varun Negi)